Hello Hello friends
my name is Mans Rani and I am Paisa
WhatsApp my father is
in the insurance field since third year today I have
brought another new topic for you whose name is
Tiji Medical Insurance Policy so let's
start Tata
festival policy gives you global cover with it
you don't have any room rent
typing with it
you also get restoration benefits along with that
you get tax benefit
Mediclaim policy
benefits in case of
medical emergency
you can understand in this from one lakh to 20 lakhs
kept in between so now let's see
how much health insurance you get in Tata exam
so first of all there
is Medicare second kind medical product and
in today's video I am going to tell you
about Medicare health insurance policy
now let's see some of the beautiful benefits of this policy
so first of all you will get
vaccination cover after two years maximum
Rs 50 benefits
in this you will get global cover as much as share
subscribe
540 Jhal Quarsi Jasvir Kaur and
hundred percent registration will be
available
policy  You will not have to request a checkup
and those with Plus will have to undergo a
tele-medical examination.
Subscribe
4,320 is an important point. Airplane fit
tax benefit will give you ₹2 as such. Income
tax benefit under section 1 of
this policy has many
benefits.
Let us take this policy through an example.
So, I have taken a family floater policy in
which there are two adults and one child. I have taken a
policy period of thirty-five years on the other side for the third child.
I have taken a one-year insurance cover
for this
subscription.
So, let us now see some more features of this policy
like, in
news treatment, you will get up to
50 hospitalizations. Ambulance cover, you will get up to 30
hospitalizations.
You will also get the option of infection treatment.
Prevent hospitalization is 6 days
and 90 days respectively. Organ
donor will also get up to 50
hospitalizations. You will get
infection treatment.
You will get
2%
maximum 21 hours after two years.
Boys travel
policy and observe an accident death.  The
benefit will be available to you today. Add-on
second opinion. You will recover only one was in
this policy year. Let us now talk about the
policy terms in this plan. So
minimum
nine different styles and maximum entry
and live entry 65 years. You
can take life-long like and subscribe policy and in this you have one to
three years
waiting period. Initial waiting
period is 30 days. Listed in Assistance
Banking Pranam is 225 forums and
pre-existing wedding friends
can be your 361. Let us now talk about
exclusions. In medical research, your
job is external disease or defects.
Normally, any person who comments,
attempts breach of law with
criminal
subscription, it comes
under non-medical, international injury
or attempted suicide.
If any unknown person comments, but
with criminal or there is any treatment, there is a
medical practitioner. Its
difference is
that I hope  I hope that you like me, my
channel and my videos.
Thank you very much for watching my videos and if you have
not subscribed to my channel yet then
subscribe quickly and
press the bell icon and I
will always bring such videos for you. Thank you, have a
nice day.